good day today's dates the 9th of May
2012 and uh we're just trying to show
you the
magnetic separation of the water you
look at the water coming out you'll see
it becoming all individual
droplets and bring it up to
its peak
see as it comes out of the out of the
unit it's doing all sorts of weird mle
stuff so the magnetic
alignment
there and if I bring my hand up and just
bring it into like into a feather
stage you'll see
the
water should
show quite a lot there of just how well
it just
separates each individual
particle so I'll find a
Mist
there or just up into the Blue Sky you
can see that
twisting into itself which is what it
does
all right so this is magnetic alignment
with the three magnets in
it just reduce my
hand just to show the difference in the
pressure so it's just hitting my hand
and just forming a
fan at that point just to show
you like okay too
easy see what you make of this on
YouTube